<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>World of Warcraft on Faarao.net</title>
    <link>https://blog.faarao.net/categories/world-of-warcraft/</link>
    <description>Recent content in World of Warcraft on Faarao.net</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.faarao.net/categories/world-of-warcraft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Antorus Progress</title>
      <link>https://blog.faarao.net/2017/12/19/antorus-progress/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.faarao.net/2017/12/19/antorus-progress/</guid>
      <description>The couple first weeks of Antorus progression are now behind me and the raid still feels rather simple. The new mechanics introduced by the mythic difficulty so far have been trivial though to be fair we are not that far into the raid yet with only five bosses down.
There are some bosses I&amp;rsquo;m still looking forward to though, namely Kin&amp;rsquo;garoth, Varimathras and Circle of Shivarra. They all had potential on heroic already and will be interesting to see them with more proper damage and healing tuning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Antorus</title>
      <link>https://blog.faarao.net/2017/12/05/antorus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.faarao.net/2017/12/05/antorus/</guid>
      <description>Week one of Antorus has come and gone and with it the first impressions of the new raid. Only on heroic so far as mythic isn&amp;rsquo;t out yet, but still.
So far the raid hasn&amp;rsquo;t offered many real challenges, with probably the most noteworthy fight being the Coven of Shivarra. That boss fight has the potential for some really nasty overlaps on heroic causing problems and almost instant wipes. I&amp;rsquo;m really looking forward to seeing it on mythic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking for a guild</title>
      <link>https://blog.faarao.net/2017/11/23/gildensuche/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.faarao.net/2017/11/23/gildensuche/</guid>
      <description>So the last week or so has been rather annoying as I ended up leaving the guild I was in and have been looking for a new one. Sadly, the search has gone rather terribly so far, though I have a few leads still. I&amp;rsquo;m really hoping one of those pans out, as it would be rather sad to miss out on the early progress in Antorus since that&amp;rsquo;s usually the most fun time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kil&#39;jaeden down!</title>
      <link>https://blog.faarao.net/2017/11/12/kj-tot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.faarao.net/2017/11/12/kj-tot/</guid>
      <description>This post is acutally quite late as we already killed him on Wednesday, however I figured it was still worth making. So indeed, Kil&amp;rsquo;jaeden finally down after some 300+ wipes and now we finally get a small breather before Antorus comes out. Well, kind of, since we are hopefully re-killing Kil&amp;rsquo;jaeden before Antorus comes out to give the people that didn&amp;rsquo;t have the chance to be there an opportunity to get the achievement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Battle for Azeroth</title>
      <link>https://blog.faarao.net/2017/11/06/bfa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.faarao.net/2017/11/06/bfa/</guid>
      <description>Blizzcon came and went and with it the announcment of a new expansion for World of Warcraft, Battle for Azeroth. And again they are talking about focusing on the fight between the Horde and the Alliance, this time with actual new game mechanics to emphasize that fight, specifically Warfronts and Island Expeditions though the latter don&amp;rsquo;t have quite as heavy an emphasis but still involve doing that exploration while fighting against a team from the opposite faction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kil&#39;jaeden the Deceiver</title>
      <link>https://blog.faarao.net/2017/11/05/kj/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.faarao.net/2017/11/05/kj/</guid>
      <description>The last few weeks of raiding have been mostly filled with progress on Kil&amp;rsquo;jaeden. And slowly I am getting slightly frustrated and strangely enough, bored, with this boss. The fight requires a decent amount of attention though not quite on the levels of Mistress or Maid however everything just happens over such a long span of time that actually getting to the part we&amp;rsquo;re progressing on is gettign frustrating.
That all is slightly strange, because at the start when almost nothing was happening as we were progressing phase one, I was actually quite enjoying the boss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Avatar has Fallen</title>
      <link>https://blog.faarao.net/2017/10/11/avatar-tot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.faarao.net/2017/10/11/avatar-tot/</guid>
      <description>On Monday we finally managed to down Avatar after surprisingly few tries. Believe I personally have around 230, which seems to be quite on the low end for that boss. In the end as noted, the boss is quite simple. Sure the DPS and HPS requirements are somewhat tough, and phase one as a healer especially. But in the end, somewhat like Maiden, the kill ended up coming as a surprise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fallen Avatar</title>
      <link>https://blog.faarao.net/2017/10/03/gefallener-avatar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.faarao.net/2017/10/03/gefallener-avatar/</guid>
      <description>So we&amp;rsquo;ve gotten a lot more progress made on Avatar thanks to extending the raid lock. Honestly I&amp;rsquo;m not quite sure if it was the right move but I do want to kill Kil&amp;rsquo;jaeden before Antorus comes out so in that sense I suppose it could be helpful. And in theory at least, we should have the gear to be able to kill both bosses so it should be fine from that perspective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Maiden of Vigilance is kinda dead</title>
      <link>https://blog.faarao.net/2017/09/26/maid-tot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.faarao.net/2017/09/26/maid-tot/</guid>
      <description>So we finally managed to kill the Maiden yesterday! It felt like it was a bit too long time coming, which made finally managing it feel rather nice. At the same time, the kill was also rather anticlimactic because of how the fight works. Since it&amp;rsquo;s only the two phases rotating the whole time, there&amp;rsquo;s no real escalation built into the fight, it only requires concentration and clean play the whole time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seat of the Triumvirate</title>
      <link>https://blog.faarao.net/2017/09/23/sitz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.faarao.net/2017/09/23/sitz/</guid>
      <description>With patch 7.3 Blizzard released a new dungeon that unlocked a couple weeks ago called Seat of the Triumvirate. I haven&amp;rsquo;t had the chance to spend too much time in there with it being so new, but have managed a couple of runs in there, one on tyrannical and fortified each. And while neither run went particularily well I have to say Blizzard has created a rather fun dungeon with the exception of a couple mechanics, specifically the third boss and the trash before the second one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Maiden of Vigilance is kinda funny</title>
      <link>https://blog.faarao.net/2017/09/14/maiden/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.faarao.net/2017/09/14/maiden/</guid>
      <description>So I haven&amp;rsquo;t written much about recent raiding efforts and lots has happened (well it&amp;rsquo;s also been over a year). In that time I&amp;rsquo;ve ended up changing guilds twice and have progressed through all heroic content while it was current and am currently progressing in mythic Tomb. Specifically, we recently killed Mistress Sassz&amp;rsquo;ine and are now on Maiden of Vigilance.
Now of the two I would definitely argue Mistress is the more interesting fight, with lots going all almost the whole time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mythic&#43; changes</title>
      <link>https://blog.faarao.net/2017/07/30/mythicplus-changes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.faarao.net/2017/07/30/mythicplus-changes/</guid>
      <description>Blizzard recently made some pretty big changes to how mythic+ works, both in the way of loot and how the keys themselves handle. The big points being:
 Beating the key quickly no longer rewards more loot, rather higher level keys (15+) have a chance at giving more loot. Completing the key in time also provides one extra piece of loot. Keys no longer get depleted, rather downgraded. If you don&amp;rsquo;t complete the dungeon in time, you get a new random key one level lower.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legion prepatch</title>
      <link>https://blog.faarao.net/2016/07/25/prepatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.faarao.net/2016/07/25/prepatch/</guid>
      <description>So the prepatch arrived a few days ago and I have had some time to do raids and dungeons with the changed talents and spells. So far it has been rather excellent, which has been a slight surprise. So far the removal of Spirit has not been a bother, though admittedly the content has also been made easier so the true test will come with the Legion dungeons and raids. I actually think healing has been more enjoyable now, the flow with Holy Words and reducing their cooldown is quite satisfying though it can lead to moments of slight frustration when there has not been a sufficient need to use other healing spells and a burst of damage comes in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raiding again!</title>
      <link>https://blog.faarao.net/2016/07/16/raiding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.faarao.net/2016/07/16/raiding/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a while, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing WoW again and actually had quite a bit of fun. I leveled a warrior because I felt like tanking a bit again and during that process ended up finding a guild which I&amp;rsquo;ve been raiding with on my priest since (priest because there wasn&amp;rsquo;t a need for tanks).
And it&amp;rsquo;s all been quite excellent, the guild is fun, Hellfire Citadel has been fun to explore properly instead of in LFR.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIP Nostalrius</title>
      <link>https://blog.faarao.net/2016/05/15/nostalrius/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.faarao.net/2016/05/15/nostalrius/</guid>
      <description>So quite a bit has happened since my last post, most notably the closing of Nostalrius where I had played. Admittedly, I did not end up playing much more since my last post, primarily due to the concern of something like closing down happening. And while Nostalrius was well managed I do still have a preference to play on the official servers even though the game in some aspects feels inferior.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sometimes Vanilla tastes better</title>
      <link>https://blog.faarao.net/2015/12/16/vanilla/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.faarao.net/2015/12/16/vanilla/</guid>
      <description>So I did end up freezing my subscription again and it&amp;rsquo;ll run out on the 26th though I doubt I&amp;rsquo;ll be logging in before that. In the end what solidified it for me was dabblinga bit with a private Vanilla server again and noticing how much more fun the game felt even with all its flaws. It&amp;rsquo;s odd noticing how years of further development haven&amp;rsquo;t really successfully added all that much that would motivate me to play and rather conversely succeeded in taking some of those motivating factors away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time&#39;s gone by</title>
      <link>https://blog.faarao.net/2015/11/30/time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.faarao.net/2015/11/30/time/</guid>
      <description>Things have been rather slow lately. After BRF, I haven&amp;rsquo;t really participated in raids which is a tad unfortunate. This is partially because as far as I can tell, there haven&amp;rsquo;t really been further raids organised in the guild or they&amp;rsquo;ve been unfortunately too late for my schedule.
However, I&amp;rsquo;ve not been completely idle, there has been some running of LFR which has lead to somewhat upgraded rings on both the priest &amp;amp; druid (still the 690 variant though).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blackrock Foundry happened</title>
      <link>https://blog.faarao.net/2015/09/28/brf-happened/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.faarao.net/2015/09/28/brf-happened/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, some raiding did actually manage to happen, kind of. A Blackrock Foundry normal run was started, sadly only five people from the guild showed up. This time however, the raid leader decided to PUG the rest of the group so it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a completely wasted effort and we (well, I) did get to experience the raid! Well, as said, kind of. While I stayed for the whole raid and we did clear all of it, at the end it was only me with one other guild member.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raiding progress (or lack thereof)</title>
      <link>https://blog.faarao.net/2015/09/20/raiding-progress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.faarao.net/2015/09/20/raiding-progress/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s been little progress since my last update. No further raids have happened so far, though there is one scheduled for tonight though only with two people signed up. I&amp;rsquo;ve made decent progress on the Talon Queen title, needing only ~3000 more reputation &amp;amp; I&amp;rsquo;ll be getting around 2000 from tomorrow&amp;rsquo;s Heroic Skyreach. As the dungeon event is ending, I&amp;rsquo;ll probably end up grinding the rest of the reputation out in the world as I haven&amp;rsquo;t bothered putting together a group for the Mythic variant of Skyreach yet and probably won&amp;rsquo;t end up doing that before the event is over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leveling complete! Gearing &amp; Raid attempts</title>
      <link>https://blog.faarao.net/2015/09/16/levelled/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.faarao.net/2015/09/16/levelled/</guid>
      <description>The last couple of weeks have gone by rather quickly, it seems. Much of that time seems to have gone with WoW, which for the time being seems to have captured my interest again which has been rather fun. As noted previously, I had started leveling a druid and managed to get to 100 almost a week ago now, last Friday morning. Leveling was one hell of a ride, I chose to do it primarily through dungeons though that stopped once I reached WoD levels, partially due to the item level restrictions for entering dungeons and partially due to long queue times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wild Growth</title>
      <link>https://blog.faarao.net/2015/09/04/wild-growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.faarao.net/2015/09/04/wild-growth/</guid>
      <description>I started leveling a Druid, and so far it&amp;rsquo;s been progressing quite well. I&amp;rsquo;ve managed to get all the way to 64, been doing dungeoning since I hit 15 and unlocked the dungeon finder. It&amp;rsquo;s been a blast so far, somehow managing to capture quite a lot of what I used to like about healing, though I&amp;rsquo;ve been able to completly ignore mana management as mana seems to be rather limitless at lower levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Returning to World of Warcraft</title>
      <link>https://blog.faarao.net/2015/09/01/returning-to-wow/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.faarao.net/2015/09/01/returning-to-wow/</guid>
      <description>So, I ended up playing World of Warcraft again after taking a break (again) about a month or two into the current expansion (Warlords of Draenor). I had decided to take the break because I didn&amp;rsquo;t have anything to do that interested me at the time and ended up returning because I got the inspiration to start leveling some more classes to see if I could find something that I could see myself playing a bit more.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>